Guide to the Neal Lane papers, 1998-2001, MS 502 MS 502
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: OSTP, NSF, Rice, other subject files, 1964-2000
  - Scripps Institution of Oceanography - San Diego, California, March 14, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Scripps Institution of Oceanography - San Diego, California, March 14, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Scripps Institute Distinguished Lecture - La Jolla, California, March 15, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Scripps Institute Distinguished Lecture - La Jolla, California, March 15, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Scripps Institute Distinguished Lecture - La Jolla, California, March 15, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Scripps Institute Distinguished Lecture - La Jolla, California, March 15, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Alvin Dive - Santa Catalina, California, March 16-17, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Alvin Dive - Santa Catalina, California, March 16-17, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Alvin Dive - Santa Catalina, California, March 16-17, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Alvin Dive - Santa Catalina, California, March 16-17, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Rutgers University, April 8, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Rutgers University, April 8, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Rutgers University, April 8, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - U.S. First Robotic Competition - Orlando, FL, April 19-21, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - U.S. First Robotic Competition - Orlando, FL, April 19-21, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Yale Symposium for D. Allan Bromley's Birthday - New Haven, Connecticut, April 26-27, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - G-7 - Scotland, U.K., May 15-16, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - G-7 - Scotland, U.K., May 15-16, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - G-7 - Scotland, U.K., May 15-16, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - G-7 - Scotland, U.K., May 15-16, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - G-7 - Scotland, U.K., May 15-16, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - G-7 - Scotland, U.K., May 15-16, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Europe, May 14-23, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Europe, May 14-23, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Europe, May 14-23, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Alexander Von Humboldt Association of America - Madison, Wisconsin, May 30-June 1, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Morgan State University, June 4, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Inauguration of Gregorian Telescope - Arecibo, Puerto Rico, June 14, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Inauguration of Gregorian Telescope - Arecibo, Puerto Rico, June 14, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Fermilab - Batavia, Illinois, July 14, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Alaska, August 5-8, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Alaska, August 5-8, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Alaska, August 5-8, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Alaska, August 5-8, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Alaska, August 5-8, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Alaska, August 5-8, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Santa Fe Institute, August 23-24, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Santa Fe Institute, August 23-24, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Santa Fe Institute, August 23-24, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Santa Fe Institute, August 23-24, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - National Association of Biology Teachers Meeting - Minneapolis, Minnesota, October 11, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - National Association of Biology Teachers Meeting - Minneapolis, Minnesota, October 11, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - 25th Anniversary of Lubbock Chapter of Achievement Rewards for College Scientists - Texas Tech University, October 15-16, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - 25th Anniversary of Lubbock Chapter of Achievement Rewards for College Scientists - Texas Tech University, October 15-16, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - 25th Anniversary of Lubbock Chapter of Achievement Rewards for College Scientists - Texas Tech University, October 15-16, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Washington University, University of Missouri, October 17-18, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Washington University, University of Missouri, October 17-18, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Washington University, University of Missouri, October 17-18, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Washington University, University of Missouri, October 17-18, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Joint High-Level Committee Meeting/Gemini Telescopes - Tokyo, Japan and Mauna Kea, Hawaii, October 1997 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Joint High-Level Committee Meeting/Gemini Telescopes - Tokyo, Japan and Mauna Kea, Hawaii, October 1997 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Joint High-Level Committee Meeting/Gemini Telescopes - Tokyo, Japan and Mauna Kea, Hawaii, October 1997 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Joint High-Level Committee Meeting brochures - Tokyo, Japan, October 21-24, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Joint High-Level Committee Meeting brochures - Tokyo, Japan, October 21-24, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Joint High-Level Committee Meeting brochures - Tokyo, Japan, October 21-24, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Gemini Site Visit brochures - Mauna Kea, Hawaii, October 25-November 1, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Gemini Site Visit brochures - Mauna Kea, Hawaii, October 25-November 1, 1997 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Frank Rhodes Symposium - Cornell University, May 21-25, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Frank Rhodes Symposium - Cornell University, May 21-25, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Subcommittee on Basic Research, Committee on Science - Oakridge, Tennessee, June 1, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Subcommittee on Basic Research, Committee on Science - Oakridge, Tennessee, June 1, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Symposium on Molecular Spectroscopy - Ohio State University, June 13-14, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - LIGO Ceremony - Baton Rouge, Louisiana, July 5-6, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Argonne National Laboratory - Chicago, Illinois, August 10, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Argonne National Laboratory - Chicago, Illinois, August 10, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Argonne National Laboratory - Chicago, Illinois, August 10, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Argonne National Laboratory - Chicago, Illinois, August 10, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Argonne National Laboratory - Chicago, Illinois, August 10, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Penn State University, September 8-9, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Penn State University, September 8-9, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - Symposium on Research Funding - Ottawa, Canada, September 14, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Symposium on Research Funding - Ottawa, Canada, September 14, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - University of Texas - Austin, September 17-18, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - University of Texas - Austin, September 17-18, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - University of Texas - Austin, September 17-18, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - United Kingdom and France, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - United Kingdom and France, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - United Kingdom and France, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - United Kingdom and France, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - United Kingdom and France, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - United Kingdom and France, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Paris, France, September 26-27, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Paris, France, September 26-27, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Paris, France, September 26-27, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Europe, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Europe - brochures, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Europe - brochure: Laboratory of Molecular Biology, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Europe - Isaac Newton Institute booklet, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Europe - Isaac Newton Institute Annual Reports, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Europe - University of Cambridge, Cavendish Laboratory materials, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Europe - The Director General of Research Councils' Review of the Science Budget Portfolio, September 18-29, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - University of Tennessee, October 16, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Japan, January 11-14, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Japan, January 11-14, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Japan, January 11-14, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Japan, January 11-14, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Japan, January 11-14, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Japan, January 11-14, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Japan, January 11-14, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Japan, January 11-14, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Japan, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Japan, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Japan, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Japan, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Japan, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - China, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - China, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - China, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - China, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - China, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - China, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - China, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - China, January 14-21, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Business, Higher Education Forum - Arizona, February 9-10, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Business, Higher Education Forum - Arizona, February 9-10, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - North Carolina Town Meeting - National Science Foundation Day, February 23, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - North Carolina Town Meeting - National Science Foundation Day, February 23, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - North Carolina Town Meeting - National Science Foundation Day, February 23, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - North Carolina Town Meeting - National Science Foundation Day, February 23, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - North Carolina Town Meeting - National Science Foundation Day, February 23, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, October 17, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, October 17, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - University of Chicago, October 19-20, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - University of Chicago, October 19-20, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - North Carolina Sigma XI Town Meeting, November 1, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Fudan University (Box 79, Folder -)
  - National Natural Science Foundation of China - Guide to Programs, FY 1994 (Box 79, Folder -)
  - Brief Introduction to the State Key Laboratories and Engineering Research Centres Established in Universities of China, 1994 (Box 79, Folder -)
  - Michigan State, November 2-3, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Michigan State, November 2-3, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Washington University, St. Louis, December 6-7, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Washington University, St. Louis, December 6-7, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Washington University, St. Louis, December 6-7, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Washington University, St. Louis, December 6-7, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Washington University, St. Louis, December 6-7, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Socorro, New Mexico, December 7-9, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Women in Science Conference, December 13-15, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Women in Science Conference, December 13-15, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Women in Science Conference, December 13-15, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Baltimore, Maryland, February 9, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Baltimore, Maryland, February 9, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Morehouse College, February 15, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Puerto Rico, March 7-9, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Puerto Rico, March 7-9, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Puerto Rico, March 7-9, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Puerto Rico, March 7-9, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Puerto Rico, March 7-9, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Puerto Rico, March 7-9, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - North Carolina Sigma XI Forum, March 2-3, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - North Carolina Sigma XI Forum, March 2-3, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, March 27, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, March 27, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, March 27, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Fractal Forms (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Fractals in Science - An Introductory Course, October 1995 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Guide to Skinner and Porter's The Blue Planet: An Introduction to Earth System Science (Box 80, Folder -)
  - 31st ACS Junior Technical Meeting/16th Interdisciplinary Scientific Meeting of Puerto Rico, March 9, 1996 (Box 80, Folder -)
  - Oxford, Ohio, April 9-10, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Oxford, Ohio, April 9-10, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Oxford, Ohio, April 9-10, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - El Paso, Texas, May 3-4, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Michigan State, May 4-5, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Michigan State, May 4-5, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Oklahoma, May 12-15, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Oklahoma, May 12-15, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Oklahoma, May 12-15, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Los Alamos, May 16, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, May 17-18, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, May 17-18, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, May 17-18, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - G-7 Meeting, May 25-26, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - G-7 Meeting, May 25-26, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - G-7 Meeting, May 25-26, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - G-7 Meeting, May 25-26, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - G-7 Meeting, May 25-26, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - G-7 Meeting, May 25-26, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - G-7 Meeting, May 25-26, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - G-7 Meeting, May 25-26, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - G-7 Meeting, May 25-26, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - IBM Research Center - New York, NY, February 24, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - American Mathematical Society Annual Joint Meeting - San Diego, California, January 9-11, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - American Mathematical Society Annual Joint Meeting - San Diego, California, January 9-11, 1997 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - American Meteorological Society - Long Beach, California, May 25-26, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Los Alamos Science, 1990 (Box 81, Folder -)
  - Los Alamos Science, 1992 (Box 81, Folder -)
  - Los Alamos Science, 1994 (Box 81, Folder -)
  - Laboratory-Directed Research and Development - Los Alamos, 1994 (Box 81, Folder -)
  - 77th AMS Annual Meeting and Exhibition, Program and Guide to Exhibits - Long Beach, California, February 2-7, 1997 (Box 81, Folder -)
  - AAAS Meeting - Seattle, Washington, February 13-15, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - AAAS Meeting - Seattle, Washington, February 13-15, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - AAAS Meeting - Seattle, Washington, February 13-15, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - University of California - San Diego, February 22-24, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - University of California - San Diego, February 22-24, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - University of California - San Diego, February 22-24, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - University of Colorado - Denver, March 6-7, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - University of Colorado - Denver, March 6-7, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - University of Colorado - Denver, March 6-7, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - University of Colorado - Denver, March 6-7, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - University of Colorado - Denver, March 6-7, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Pitcon Symposium - Atlanta, Georgia, March 16-17, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Pitcon Symposium - Atlanta, Georgia, March 16-17, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Pitcon Symposium - Atlanta, Georgia, March 16-17, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - San Antonio, Texas and Oklahoma, April 14-15, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - San Antonio, Texas and Oklahoma, April 14-15, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Vanderbilt University - Nashville, Tennessee, April 17-19, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Vanderbilt University - Nashville, Tennessee, April 17-19, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Vanderbilt University - Nashville, Tennessee, April 17-19, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - G-7 Meeting - Berlin, May 11-13, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - G-7 Meeting - Berlin, May 11-13, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - G-7 Meeting - Berlin, May 11-13, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - G-7 Meeting - Berlin, May 11-13, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Moscow, St. Petersburg, May 15-20, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Netherlands, May 21, 1997 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Japan, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Japan, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Japan, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Japan, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Japan, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Japan - Riken brochures, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Japan - RITE brochures, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Japan - National Laboratory for High Energy Physics brochures, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Japan - Education in Japan booklet, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Japan - International Visitors Guide, University of Tsukuba, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Japan - brochures, May 6-12, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii, May 13, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Hawaii, May 13, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Hawaii, May 13, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Hawaii, May 13, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Japan/Hawaii Briefing Book, May 9-17, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Japan/Hawaii Briefing Book, May 9-17, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Princeton University, May 23-24, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Princeton University, May 23-24, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Princeton University, May 23-24, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Princeton University, May 23-24, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - SSRC Board Meeting - New York, June 6, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - University of Alabama, June 18, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Bates College - Maine, June 22-23, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Bates College - Maine, June 22-23, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - NCAR visit, August 4, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - NCAR visit, August 4, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - NCAR visit, August 4, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Colorado, August 4-9, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Colorado, August 4-9, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Alaska, August 21-27, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Alaska, August 21-27, 1994 (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Brussels, May 20, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Germany, May 21-22, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Germany, May 21-22, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Germany, May 21-22, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Germany, May 21-22, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Sacramento, California, May 28, 1996 (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Epscor Meeting - Montana, May 28-June 1, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Epscor Meeting - Montana, May 28-June 1, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Epscor Meeting - Montana, May 28-June 1, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Epscor Meeting - Montana, May 28-June 1, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Epscor Meeting - Montana, May 28-June 1, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Epscor Meeting - Montana, May 28-June 1, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Ohio State University, June 5-8, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Ohio State University, June 5-8, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Ohio State University, June 5-8, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Ohio State University, June 5-8, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Princeton, July 10-11, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Princeton, July 10-11, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Woods Hole, Massachussetts, July 23, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Woods Hole, Massachussetts, July 23, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Woods Hole, Massachussetts, July 23, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Spain/Canary Islands, June 29-July 7, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - University of Wisconsin, September 5-6, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Cornell University, September 19-20, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Cornell University, September 19-20, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Cornell University, September 19-20, 1996 (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - EPSCOR Meeting Conference Proceedings/brochures - South Dakota, November 8-9, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - EPSCOR Meeting, A Proceedings - South Dakota, November 8-9, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - EPSCOR Meeting materials - South Dakota, November 8-9, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - EPSCOR Meeting materials - South Dakota, November 8-9, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 34)
  - Supercomputing - Portland, Oregon, November 16, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 35)
  - Supercomputing - Portland, Oregon, November 16, 1993 (Box 84, Folder 36)
  - Observatorios Astrofisicos de Canarias (Box 84, Folder 37)
  - National Academy of Science Council Meeting - Irvine, California, February 17, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineerng Symposium - Irvine, California, February 18, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - AAAS Annual Meeting - San Francisco, California, February 19, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - AAAS Annual Meeting - San Francisco, California, February 19, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Conacyt Meeting, February 21-23, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Conacyt Meeting, February 21-23, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Conacyt Meeting, February 21-23, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Conacyt Meeting, February 21-23, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Second DeLange Conference - Rice University, February 28-March 2, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Second DeLange Conference - Rice University, February 28-March 2, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Yale University, March 11, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - American Physical Society Meeting - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, March 23, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - University of Michigan - Ford Foundation, March 28-29, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - University of Michigan - Ford Foundation, March 28-29, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - University of Michigan - Ford Foundation, March 28-29, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - University of Michigan - Ford Foundation, March 28-29, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - International Science Festival, Sigma Xi Lecture - Scotland, April 5-9, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - International Science Festival, Sigma Xi Lecture - Scotland, April 5-9, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - International Science Festival, Sigma Xi Lecture - Scotland, April 5-9, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - International Science Festival, Sigma Xi Lecture - Scotland, April 5-9, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - University of Virginia - New Alliances for Economic Development, May 2, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Alaska - brochures, August 21-27, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Alaska - brochures, August 21-27, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Alaska - brochures, August 21-27, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 24)
  - Alaska - brochures, August 21-27, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 25)
  - NCAR Conference - Oregon, September 18-21, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 26)
  - NCAR Conference - Oregon, September 18-21, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 27)
  - NCAR Conference - Oregon, September 18-21, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 28)
  - University of Washington - Seattle, September 20-21, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 29)
  - University of Washington - Seattle, September 20-21, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 30)
  - Caltech Associates Dinner, September 29, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 31)
  - Caltech Associates Dinner, September 29, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 32)
  - National High Magnetic Field Laboratory - Florida, September 30-October 1, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 33)
  - National High Magnetic Field Laboratory - Florida, September 30-October 1, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 34)
  - IISME Panel Discussion, October 14-15, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 35)
  - IISME Panel Discussion, October 14-15, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 36)
  - Texas A, October 17-18, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Texas A, October 17-18, 1994 (Box 86, Folder 2)